{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite colour?",
      "answer1": "A) Red",
      "answer2": "B) Black",
      "answer3": "C) Pink",
      "answer4": "D) Brown",
      "correct": "A) Red"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite clothing style?",
      "answer1": "A) Over-sized baggy clothes",
      "answer2": "B) Tight clothes",
      "answer3": "C) Tutu dress/skirt",
      "answer4": "D) 2000's Y2K style",
      "correct": "A) Over-sized baggy clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is her favourite artist?",
      "answer1": "A) Kendrick Lamar",
      "answer2": "B) Tyla",
      "answer3": "C) Tyler Swift",
      "answer4": "D) Uncle Waffles",
      "correct": "B) Tyla"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite brand?",
      "answer1": "A) Nike",
      "answer2": "B) Jordan",
      "answer3": "C) Calvin Klein",
      "answer4": "D) Puma",
      "correct": "C) Calvin Klein"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite song?",
      "answer1": "A) I was a bad girl by JoJo Siwa",
      "answer2": "B) Truth or Dare by Tyla",
      "answer3": "C) Mocking Bird by Eminem",
      "answer4": "D) Wadi Busa by Uncle Waffles",
      "correct": "B) Truth or Dare by Tyla"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite cartoon?",
      "answer1": "A) Sofia The First",
      "answer2": "B) Teen Titans Go",
      "answer3": "C) Mr Magoo",
      "answer4": "D) Regular Show",
      "correct": "A) Sofia The First"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the celebrity she wants to meet?",
      "answer1": "A) Sabrina Carpenter",
      "answer2": "B) Tyler Swift",
      "answer3": "C) Tyla",
      "answer4": "D) Kendrick Lamar",
      "correct": "D) Kendrick Lamar"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite phone brand?",
      "answer1": "A) Huawei",
      "answer2": "B) Apple (iPhone)",
      "answer3": "C) Samsung",
      "answer4": "D) Le Popotane",
      "correct": "B) Apple (iPhone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is her favourite Youtuber?",
      "answer1": "A) SSSniperwolf",
      "answer2": "B) The RSA Boys",
      "answer3": "C) Ghost Hlubi",
      "answer4": "D) Ashley Plays",
      "correct": "D) Ashley Plays"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is her favourite restaurant?",
      "answer1": "A) Ocean Basket",
      "answer2": "B) KFC",
      "answer3": "C) Chicken Licken",
      "answer4": "D) Mc Donald's",
      "correct": "A) Ocean Basket"
    }
  ]
}